const questions = [
    {question:"Fill in the blank to finish the quote. 'Hello. My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my ____. Prepare to die." , answer: "father"},
    {question:"Who wrote The Princess Bride?" , answer: "William Goldman"},
    {question:"Which actor was almost cast in the role of Fezzik instead of Andre Roussimoff?" , answer: "Arnold Schwarzenegger"},
    {question:"What type of injury did Mandy Patinkin sustain while attempting to hold back laughter during scenes with Billy Crystal?" , answer: "a bruised rib"},
    {question:"What size is the rodent found in the fire swamp?" , answer: "unusual size"},
    {question:"Fill in the blank to complete the quote. 'Stop rhyming, I mean it.' 'Anybody want a _____?'" , answer: "peanut"},
    {question:"Which creatures in the film were not in the original novel?" , answer: "shrieking eels"},
    {question:"Who were Miracle Max and his wife Valerie named after?" , answer: "William Goldman's parents"},
    {question:"What are the names of the two rival kingdoms in the movie?" , answer: "Florin and Guilder"},
    {question:"Which fictional vigilante inspired the costume for the Dread Pirate Roberts?" , answer: "Zorro"},
];
console.log(questions) 
console.log(games) 
const response = window.prompt("Can you answer the following Princess Bride trivia question?");
